Hi, my name is Lauren, and today, I'm going to go over how to keep from going bald.
There are many things that you can do within today's society in order to maintain the hair that you have in order to keep it.
There is a shampooing system called Nioxin, which actually helps stimulate the hair follicle and helps your hair grow.
You use it as a regular...it's a three-step process that you can use.
You can buy it at many different beauty destinations, and you would just simply shampoo, condition, and use it on a daily basis in order to keep the hair that you have and grow in more hair per follicle.
Rogaine is also another great choice.
It is a treatment that you would use.
It is a mousse treatment that you put on your hair.
It will also help you grow hair by stimulating your scalp.
A home remedy would be honey mixed with egg yolk.
You would simply massage it into your scalp and hair for about...and leave it on for about a half an hour, and then you would rinse it out.
Almond oil is also a great way to keep the hair that you have and to help grow more hair. You, again, would massage this into your scalp and for...I usually would massage for about 10 to 15 minutes.
It really promotes blood circulation when you stimulate your scalp and you move it.
Massage is pretty important because it opens up that blood flow and it also helps unrestrict your pores.
Apple cider vinegar and sage tea, you can use as a rinse.
That will help your hair grow, so it'll help you keep the hair that you have and have it grow very healthy.
Also, you may want to consult your doctor if you continue to experience hair loss.
Consulting your doctor would also help, whether or not it is from any medications that you're on for you to be losing your hair or any sort of vitamin deficiencies.
Your doctor will be able to figure out what could be the internal cause of your hair loss and lead you in the right direction in order to prevent any more hair loss.
And that is how you prevent from going bald.